<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>TextMate, by Programmers, for Efficiency Experts</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2005/12/22/textmate-by-programmers-for-efficiency-experts</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="2c4d121033d9f4d31ee231a8746a259e" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>TextMate, by Programmers, for Efficiency Experts</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>framnwebs@cox.net</author>
      <description>Just wanted to say awesome job on the site design, I like it. Also wanted to give a :thumbsup: on your choice of editors. TextMate is an extremely useful editor that is fast, lightweight, and very configurable. Truly is the missing OS X editor! (It just works.)

It's my pleasure to turn you on to another great theme for TextMate that you are almost certain to compare against Hallows Eve. It's called &lt;a href="http://encytemedia.com/blog/articles/2006/01/03/textmate-vibrant-ink-theme-and-prototype-bundle"&gt;Vibrant Ink&lt;/a&gt;, and can be downloaded &lt;a href="http://encytemedia.com/blog/articles/2006/01/03/textmate-vibrant-ink-theme-and-prototype-bundle"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.

Enjoy!  (and keep up the great work!)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="132.185.240.121" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>thisisspam@mac.com</author>
      <description>If you're using TextMate you're using a Mac. If you're using a Mac, and are using TextMate, you're probably the sort of person who's installed Apple's developer tools.... in which case, I urge you to have a play with FileMerge (in /Developer/Applications/Utilities) for comparing changes to files. It will blow your mind !</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Well I'm not sure if the author has changed some color schemes or perhaps my eyes are just getting so bad that I need the contrast boost, but I am now using the Vibrant Ink bundle. It really does shine in when coding Ruby and RAILs classes.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="217.205.66.68" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>max.mitchell@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I've watched the screencasts. I've seen the Subversion integration. I've seen the Rails and Textmate cheatsheets. I'm moving to a Mac and getting TextMate.

I like Emacs. I like Linux. I'm keeping them. But I can get a puny iBook and have a rad time.

Posts like this just make it seem so obvious!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.17.243.209" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ericob@possibilityengine.com</author>
      <description>You wrote "For instance, rather than using man dig or man rsync from the terminal, just select it in TextMate and hit Control-H."

How do you get this to work consistently?  I *swear* that it happened once for me, and now never again.  The source consulted when you press ^H seems to depend on what language the current document is tagged as.  w3.org doesn't know what "SSH" means, for example.  I tried changing the language tag to Perl or C but that didn't give me results from man either.

Any thoughts?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Those are the two that I use the most. So when you are shell scripting, you get man pages. But most of the time too, I have a "scratch" plain text window open, sometimes for cut and copying text and also for man pages. Hope that helps. Also, have you done a subversion checkout of the bundles?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.17.243.209" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ericob@possibilityengine.com</author>
      <description>Ken asked "...have you done a subversion checkout of the bundles?"  Nope.  Using a plain text window, ^H give me a tool tip reading Couldn't find documentation for "ssh" (or whatever command I entered.  Hmm.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You know, this was a very interesting problem. Sure enough in my TextMate too (OS X 10.4.6) all the man pages stopped working. Here is what I found out. Go inside the bundle editor, go to the commands for "Unix Shell", click on the one labeled "Documentation for Word / Selection (man)". In here, if I removed this line below my man pages started to work again&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;code type="bash"&gt;
export MANSECT=2:3:4:5:6:7:8:9 # exclude shell commands
&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another note, while searching the TextMate lists, I found this interesting utility called Bwana. It will show all the man pages linked together in safari. Good god is this bad ass! I really suggest checking it out too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.bruji.com/bwana/"&gt;http://www.bruji.com/bwana/&lt;/a&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.17.243.209" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ericob@possibilityengine.com</author>
      <description>Huh!  Well, that worked for me also.  Can  you say what clued you in to this being the problem?  Other than just randomly deleting stuff?  :)

Yes, I know of Bwana.  A cool program.  Looking up a man page while working in TextMate is certainly not something I do very often (since I'm mostly using TM to edit web pages!) but since I was "supposed" to be able to do it, I wondered why it didn't work!

Thanks!  My next TextMate mystery is why control escape does nothing (it is supposed to evoke the "gear" menu).  It works in a newly-created account, so I'm guessing "something" that I've added to my main account has "stolen" that keybinding.  Although I have yet to find any other place it does anything, or any preferences dialog that mentions that shortcut.  I wish there was a solution other than brute force to figure this one out!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-27-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>I figured it had to be in there somewhere. So I coped out that command into a TextMate shell doc and started executing it in different fashions to see what that script did. I excel in taking things apart. Creating new things is hard work for me :)

Perhaps you should try whacking your TM prefs in your ~/Library/Preferences to see if that helps with your other problem. Maybe even rebuilding your /Library/Application Support/TextMate directory.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="7-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>The Best Font for Mac Programmers, ProFont</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/1/11/the-best-font-for-mac-programmers-profont</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="2d89162b3fbe5733a39e3fd2b5a0511d" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>The Best Font for Mac Programmers, ProFont</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>for@you.com</author>
      <description>I couldn't get profont working for OS X. The archive you link to looks very OS 9'ish and every sub folder is the archive was empty.

Another good location for fixed width/terminal/programming fonts is this site: http://www.lowing.org/fonts/

Personally I've grown to like the Anonymous font: http://www.ms-studio.com/FontSales/anonymous.html</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>I fixed the ProFont download on this site and I am really going to take a look at anonymous too. Thanks for those two great link.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.114.239.187" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>root@mac.com</author>
      <description>I actualyl find it to be about perfect for a developer font.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>And at 10pt it was a little to hard on the eye. The equal sign kerning was right up agains the other letters and overall it was a strain to see. I did like it at 12pt, but that is to large for my work space, even with my bad eyes. Thanks for the heads up!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="80.213.49.228" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>lindsve@bluezone.no</author>
      <description>Thanks for the tip about the Anonymous font. Currently I'm using Andale Mono 11pt as my font in TextMate and likes it a lot. Not sure where I got it from though...</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="209.20.249.115" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>wildbasil@pobox.com</author>
      <description>DejaVu rapidly-developing open-source free-of-cost font family, including a monospaced font, spawned from Bitstream Vera. DejaVu has many characters for many languages &amp; specialties. Some versions of Linux are making DejaVu their default font.

http://dejavu.sourceforge.net/


</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-221-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2006 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was just reading a post on the &lt;a href="http://macromates.com/blog/archives/2006/04/06/thanks-apple/"&gt;TextMate blog about Bitstream Vera Sans Mono&lt;/a&gt; and tried it out. It was OK looking at first but I like my font size around 10px and it did not appear to compete well with ProFont. For instance I did not like zeros and various meta characters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just downloaded DejuVu and had the exact same experience. At 10px it was terrible looking. At 12px it got better, but I still did not like the look of those damned zeros and more importantly, 10px is what I need. Thanks for the head up though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="21-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Cooking with Drupal</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/1/28/cooking-with-drupal</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="fae38278a93d8b3bcc39aa90ab3f3a7c" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Cooking with Drupal</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="128.189.189.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joshk@efn.org</author>
      <description>Hey ken!

We're up here at Drupalcon in Vancouver making a site on the spot and we're going to use your theme. It's quite something! Thanks for making and contributing it!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>And thanks for the kudos on the theme! Please help me out by testing it. I would love to have some feedback on any features or code that is needed. 

BTW, I noticed you have a WordPress blog. What is up with that?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="84.41.137.187" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>roel@assenmacher.nl</author>
      <description>Hi Ken,

First of all, great theme you made.
I am going to use it for our new site, but I have a question:

We would love to use a Flash movie as the site header, instead of a image. We have tried several ways to realise this, but we couldn't get it working.

Is there a way to use a Flash movie as header?

Thank!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>That is a good question. I had always anticipated that people would like to customize that image. Perhaps even with a JavaScript fade technique of a few images. Right now that image is in a DIV that is specifying a background (the image you see) with CSS. The value for that CSS declaration is in a couple of places since it is (1) a theme option and (2) a user defined style sheet option. Let's take into account that you are using the default meta theme (green) in your Drupal install.

You can find the CSS declaration for the background in the "pagestructure.css" file around line 302 for the #masthead-image and the image is loaded via that url variable. Although I have never tried, I "suppose" you could change that to a .swf file. I have never experimented using a Flash file in a CSS declaration. I do know however, that if you did do that, you would loose the ability to detect for it since the flash movie would not be in it's normal OBJECT or EMBED tags within the flow of the XHTML.

You also have the option of taking that DIV and CSS declaration and giving it a specific width (experiment with this starting around 850px) and then putting another DIV in that with an absolute position and the same specified width and height and use that to load your flash code into the XHTML. If you took this route, you would more than likely lose the ability to have a site that worked as a liquid/fixed width user specified layout, the MetaTools at the top.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.53.86.230" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joeiscoffee@yahoo.com</author>
      <description>First, thanks for sharing this impressive work.

I've got a fresh install of 4.7 (last install I did was 4.3) anyway my question is how do I get the "Post new comment" to appear at the bottom of a comment as it does here and elsewhere?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.53.86.230" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joeiscoffee@yahoo.com</author>
      <description>As usual after asking a lame question I find the answer.

Thanks again for the outstanding theme.Any chance you can flesh out and improve the forum look with your theme?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>I know exactly what you mean. Sometimes I think Drupal can be a click-a-thon when it comes to turning things on and off. I definitely will work on the forums appearance. Things at the top of my to do are adding more conventions for authors into the blog feature. I'll then get bored and turn to the forums :)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="212.189.37.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Hi Ken,

Thanks for your answer...
I found out that it is not possible to use a flash movie from a css file. So we came with another idea, we start using multiple images and let them change every 5 or 10 second or so. Nice idea, but also not working from css. It seems you can only set the background tag with a hard image file, and no php, swf or js file...

So, someone came with another idea: why not change the theme every 5 seconds. It seemed do-able, because the theme can be set by pressing a button, so why not automatically, using a timer script.

Now, the problem is not the timer script, but setting the theme. We have tried several ways, but cannot find the correct command to set the theme from the php file.
Can you give us a little push in the right direction to do so?

Thanks again!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>I tell you what. Over the next few days I'll be working on some upgrades and a bit of cross-browser testing with this theme. When doing so, I'll add another layer DIV in the masthead that should work as an alternate image (themeable area) by inserting media within the structural content, the page.template file. In this way, the media can be inserted directly into the HTML like most are used to which means easy access to multiple images via a JS fade or "maybe" even a flash file. If you can wait a few days?

BTW, I do not like the PHP solution. I think it will not work since it requires a page refresh which is one of the reason I never went with a PHP-based stylesheet switcher. Typically you want to stay in the realm of JS and DOM level 2 so you can actively change page presentation without a refresh.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="124.177.111.118" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>nywf06@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I've hit a bit of an obstacle with the Meta theme. It looks delicious in firefox, but if I open it in IE, it can't be read. Funny thing is, it only applies to the front page, node. (see www.nywf.org.au) Any suggestions as to how I can overcome this snag? Most of my users will be IE based. Thanks for your help, and especially for the gorgeous theme!
Cheers
Kat</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I can see in my code that the document tree in the "contentarea-bounding" DIV goes to these there levels.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
contentarea-bounding
  - contentarea-left
  - contentarea-middle1
  - contentarea-right1
contentbgbottom-bounding
  - etc...
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your document tree on your site looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
contentarea-bounding
  - contentarea-left
  - contentarea-middle1
  - contentbgbottom-bounding
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where you nested the "contentarea-right1" DIV, I'm not sure. But somehone you altered the structure of your site and this theme is very pickey, moving one thing changes alot and you really have to know your CSS to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="202.172.123.77" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>killabytes@hotmail.com</author>
      <description>any chance of the above taking place?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-11" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.215.180.226" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>pogi@hoy-pare.com</author>
      <description>Hi there.. I love the theme and the work you've done for this.. However myself and a lot of the drupal community are dying to have a version 5 compatible meta theme.. Are you going to be doing this at any point?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-12" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-229-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2006 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.196.234.108" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>rob@inbox-usa.com</author>
      <description>As above, any movement on a Drupal 5 version?  I am open to paying for some work if you are available....

I left my email let me know if this is something you can do...</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="29-13" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Mini Network with a Big XServe Style</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/2/5/mini-network-with-a-big-xserve-style</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="24eb110968c7a125c76ff1e8acffa3d5" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Mini Network with a Big XServe Style</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.155.55.253" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>chocobananas@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hey! Nice website. You're definitly a CSS coding expert. Did you ever consider writing a tutorial about it?

Cheers</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>There are way too many CSS turorials already and I'd rather stick to the less talked about subjects. I learned by watching the CSS tutorials from Lynda.com. These are quite boring but it does give you foundation from which to experiement.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.108.144.52" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>cfuir-order@yahoo.com</author>
      <description>Thank you for a very informative article.  Enjoyed the rest of your site too.  One thing though:  there's a recurring misuse of the contraction "it's" in place of the correct possessive adjective "its".  I only mention it because the same error occurs on your swissdisk.com site ("Not even SwissDisk or it's employees..."), and I thought you'd want to definitely fix that one.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>But thank you very much for pointing that out. I will start to update those right away.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="80.177.101.17" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>danielhanlon@hotmail.com</author>
      <description>Whilst on the subject of grammar..... if we're correcting its/it's then surely a split infinitive also needs pointing out :-) 'definitely want to fix' perhaps?

Very good article by the way!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Thank you for that, you made my day!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="207.44.180.3" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>fred@concretewerk.com</author>
      <description>I'm just curious: from the final setup photo it looks like you've got a Linksys wireless gateway/router rather than an actual Airport Extreme Basestation(TM). Especially considering the close physical proximity of all the components, why did you chose to use wireless networking rather than  hardwired 100baseT Ethernet? I understand using the WiFi basestation for your laptop, but not at all for networking. Plus, a couple of lengths of Cat-5 is a heck of a lot cheaper than Airport modems. I really don't understand your choice of (max) 54 Mbps 802.11g over (max) 100 Mbps ethernet. And switches will work better than WiFi no matter what.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Fred, I've seen this question pop up before. The network diagram at the beginning does show that the 100baseT ethernet ports are being used. These are the public interfaces. The Airport Extreme cards are only used for the internal LAN so that I do not have to route my administrative traffic to those public interfaces on the ethernet ports. All local traffic stays on the LAN/AirPort using internal DNS.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="72.229.147.231" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>michael@pisapia.net</author>
      <description>"give you foundation to experiement from." should read " give you foundation from which to experiement."

...but on a serious note: this is one of the best posts on the subject, home networking- not split infinitives- and it is great stuff.  Thank you very much for such great instruction and please keep up the good work!!

Best regards from NYC...
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="220.253.60.184" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>kdghantous@photo.net</author>
      <description>Soon after the mini was released I had the idea that someone should do something like this. I'm very enthusiastic about low current, compact computers whether on the desktop or in the server room. The less noise and energy consumed the better, even if some performance is lost.

Next step: supercomputer mini cluster. :-D</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.245.9.223" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>djmeier@slash32.com</author>
      <description>I guess my only comment is that the wireless backend opens up a can of worms.  If I were to do this I would take that Linksys you have sitting around and throw DD-WRT or Sveasoft images on them and build a couple of non-routed VLANs.  Then to get from your public side to the WebSvr Mini add a USB Ethernet device and keep the IPoFirewire connection as the backend.  I know -- it's not straight up out of the box that way, but...  The time that would be spent hacking up that Mini might be better offset spending $28 on a USB Ethernet device (say a USB100M from Linksys).  With a CCNP and CISSP background, I would just never be able to justify an operations platform running wireless for dedicated services.

But...  Just my $0.02.  Great article though, images and page design rock!
--Dave</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.245.9.223" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>djmeier@slash32.com</author>
      <description>One more thing...

Your IP Over Firewire Connections - (192.168.1.0/25 Addresses), should be on a /30 network.  ;)

Net:  192.168.1.0 /30
Hosts: 192.168.1.1 &amp; 1.2 / 30
BC: 192.168.1.3 /30

Since they are communicating just with themselves.  I realize it's a point-to-point connection, but if you want to get down to correct networking practice, that's the way to do it!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-11" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.183.137.73" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>I've never heard of most of that stuff and I did just do a quick look around on Wikipedia and some product website. Would the wireless "backend" bother you when it is really just a backend for LAN only traffic? I mean there are really only two ways of compromising my internal LAN.

&lt;strong&gt;Method 1:&lt;/strong&gt; Hacking past my AirPort basestation from its public interface and wrecking havoc on the LAN which is technically still locked down for passwords, etc. Possible?

&lt;strong&gt;Method 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Having someone outside in the bushes or down the street with a Pringles can listening for a WEP password to break into my closed AirPort network. Do people really do this and for what gain, some database files that have an article that they can read publicly on the web?

I think the context of the network could play a very reasonable role in what amount of security one employees. But if I have missed something like how vulnerable my AirPort basestation is, I would really like to know.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-12" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="65.189.26.34" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>Lee@UnitOneNine.com</author>
      <description>Ken,

Did you have any problems with your seagate drives fitting? it said that they might not fit in the case.

I just bought 4- 300GB 7200 8MB drives and wanted to make sure they fit before i go nab a couple miniStacks.

thanks!!

lee</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-13" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-14</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Yes, I did have a small problem when putting the drives in. It was an easy fix though. All you have to do is NOT screw the drive to the internal caddy of the miniStack. Since everything is so tight it did not really need to be screwed to that caddy. Hope that helps.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-14" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.245.9.223" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>djmeier@slash32.com</author>
      <description>OK, well...  My point is that if it is a server platform the wireless solution (in my mind -- this was just my opinion, no flaming here) would just not be a good idea.  Take for example your backend doing SQL transactions.  Are you sure that all of these are done via a safe transport?  Maybe SSL for starters?  What about SQL injection vulnerabilities if that wasn't the case?  Secondly -- I know that you're solution is geared to SOHOers, and not a secure NOC environment -- I've been there.  I'm probably overly anal about security because of my job.  I work in the defense industry for a major contractor and I end up nitpicking the details out of air defense systems.  Ultimately, I posted the comment about the wired local LAN for ideas to move towards your version 2.  I think the article was great and you made use of everything out of the box (with the exception of hacking that pretty little Mini)  ;)

One last thing...  WEP?  Are you friggin' nuts?  ;)  LOL, J/K.  Your Airport should support WPA2.

I also realize that many-o-many public databases are sitting in the clear on vulnerable platforms.  The thing is -- there are so many great tools out there that are very convenient to use.  Do you really know who your neighbors are?  ;)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-15" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.161.58.127" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>info@richard5.net</author>
      <description>Just wanted to let you know that this was very informative (even with the spelling mistakes..).

I'm trying to setup something similar but started with just one mini and will see where I end up. I'm documenting as much as I can so others can use the info to setup their on server. Got mail, web and database services running and I'm curently playing wth spamassassin. 

I'll be following your efforts on this... maybe I can learn something... who knows.

 </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-16" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>And good luck with your SA configuration. One thing I've found very useful is configuring postfix is the live blacklist feature. In the OS X Server Admin, there is a feature for this and I have my mail server set to use &lt;a href="http://www.spamhaus.org/sbl/howtouse.html" rel="external" class="external-link"&gt;Spamhaus&lt;/a&gt; as a real time blacklist. I use sbl-xbl.spamhaus.org in mine. If you are configuring postfix by the CLI, I you can just add &lt;code&gt;smtpd_client_restrictions = permit_mynetworks  refect_rbl_client xbl-xbl.spamhaus.org permit&lt;/code&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-17" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-18</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="65.87.166.24" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>t413@earthlink.net</author>
      <description>This is a incredible setup, I have to say.  What software are you using to run it all, though?  Are you using Mac OS X Server for all three?  At it's lowest price, that's $500 per box and it seems like a superfluous expense seeing as most of the software you could ever want is available open source.  This site is awesome, thanks.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-18" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Good question and your right, running OS X Server on the lot does not make sense. I only have that on the Mini that handles mail and external DNS. The other two are client machines that run Apache2 copied from Apple's /opt directory and PHP 5 (entropy.ch) and MySQL 4. Thanks.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-19" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="155.97.238.217" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jared@cynicious.com</author>
      <description>I'm very close to wanting to set up server on a Mini.  Do you have a tutorial on how you did this?

&amp;lt;/Jared&amp;gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-20" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="65.189.26.34" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>Lee@UnitOneNine.com</author>
      <description>Hey, just got my 4- 300GB drives and got the lil sucker up and running no probs. thx for letting me know that they fit!

cheers,

lee
___________________
www.UnitOneNine.com</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-21" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="17.219.208.176" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>Bilbrey@Apple.com</author>
      <description>Ken,

It is not surprising to have poor wireless performance when you block the top of the Mac Mini. The openings in the top shield are the only 'holes' for the Airport and Bluetooth signals to escape the 'faraday cage' that encloses the Mac Mini. In fact, we warn that setting things on top of the Mac Mini, or otherwise blocking the wireless signal can result in reduced wireless performance.

My point is you state "...if you want to get good AirPort strength and this was a must for me, here is some helpful instructions." and this is true only if you plan to block the wireless access points on the top cover. Otherwise, the Mac Mini has very good wireless performance.

Since you have extracted the antennas from the system, you may wish to cover the openings in the top shield with copper tape to prevent either radiated emissions or susceptibility to noise.

Other than that, it is pretty cool what you are doing with the Mac Mini.

Brett</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-22" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Well who ever you are, I'm glad your not in my bushes :) I did look around and noticed that my AirPort does support WPA2 Enterprise. I could switch that over for better security, I do not think it would hurt. Thanks for the eye openers!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-23" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>That is a very good point Brett. I should have stated that "for me" I was not willing to set all the Minis up with nothing on top of them, otherwise they would all have great performance. I do think if you are looking at the mini's as servers this is worth it. For instance take a look at &lt;a href="http://www.squarebox.co.uk/thresholdFront.jpg"&gt;Perth Concert Hall in Scotland's&lt;/a&gt; setup. I found this from the &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/macmini/bigideas.html"&gt;Mac Mini Big Ideas&lt;/a&gt; page on Apple's site.

About the "faraday cage", that's a good point too. What material should I use?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-24" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="193.204.139.190" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>lucianodileonardo@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Well done!!!! That's great!!!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-25" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="62.1.245.74" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>origami@ath.forthnet.gr</author>
      <description>I'm wondering what would be the best network solution, for not having the win boxes allow direct access to the rooter, but rather having a macmini inbetween,the rooter doesn't have advanced features, and the IP isn't static as well,
I've seen an article about this recently but now I couldn't find it.

regards,</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-26" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.5.103.15" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>anonymous@anonymous.com</author>
      <description>Wav.. this is amazing setup.. very powerful inexpensive and very secure.

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-27" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.210.171.117" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>smuth@smuth.com</author>
      <description>Cool but wouldn't a G4 tower off Ebay for $175-$200 do it just as well and extra NICs are like $10. I run 1 with 3 Ethernets and wireless, it runs DNS, Windowz file sharing, firewall, and puts up a webpage for the open wireless to the public in the DMZ, all for less than $250.00. I have both a wired and wireless DMZ plus a safe local net. 

If I had a mini I'd use it to drive the TV and audio around my house. </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-28" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="209.20.249.115" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>wildbasil@pobox.com</author>
      <description>If the mini has only one FireWire port, how did you manage to use IP networking over FireWire between the database and web servers while also plugging in FireWire hard disk expansion boxes?

Are you daisy-chaining the networking and hard disks?
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-29" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>That is correct and it worked surprisingly well. It will have a performance hit at some point but honestly if the WebSvr =&gt; DB load get over a 10 megabit connection which is nothing for firewire, then I can think about rethinking things. That 10 number is untested too, I'm sure the firewire (network) traffic can go alot higher.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-30" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-31</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.54.70.106" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>iamnoskcaj@gmail.com</author>
      <description>There's no reason why he should use a /30 for a machine to machine lan connection. We're talking about what amounts to a cross-over style connection. 

If you want to categorize this as a point-to-point, I won't even argue with you. Using a /30 in a private network like this is unnecessary. In fact, it complicate the scenario. If a point-to-point internet, or wan, connection was setup by a provider, and they were assigning many networks to their various customers, using a /30 would be very appropriate, but not in such a small network like this.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-31" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="69.236.102.167" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>reeses@astrogoth.com</author>
      <description>This may or may not be a question you can answer, but you're the only person I remember who has tried something similar that blew up for me.

For various reasons that would bore most, I wanted to connect my old PowerBook to my Mini to transfer some large files back and forth, hoping that it would be faster than through my cheap Gig-E switch.

It worked fine, but then something odd happened.  I have about four firewire drives hanging off of the Mini, and the PowerBook mounted one of them.  At that point, neither machine could do anything with the drive.  I suspect it may have had something to do with the drive spinning down, going to sleep, and then being reawakened with two machines on the FW bus, but that's just a guess.

Have you had this problem with your two IP/FW nodes?  Have you heard of anyone having this problem?  If so, do you have any suggestions on avoiding it in future?

Thanks!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-32" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.6" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Hey there, I am a big fan of doing things that would bore most :)

Sadly, I have not heard of your issue before. I assume that you were using the "T" key on boot up to toggle the PowerBook into firewire disk mode? Once that happens, it should just act as another drive in the firewire chain and that you are saying that the PoweBook drive is no longer usable? Have you tried resetting the PMU or PRAM? If those do not work try resetting the NVRAM in OpenFirmware by doing Command-Option-O-F keys at startup, which brings up the Open Firmware command line interface the the command reset-nvram should do it I think.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-33" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="69.236.102.167" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>reeses@astrogoth.com</author>
      <description>My apologies for not explaining the topology accurately.

I didn't boot the PowerBook into firewire drive mode -- rather, I wanted to use it to fake screen-spanning using &lt;a href="http://synergy2.sourceforge.net/"&gt;Synergy2&lt;/a&gt;.  Since I can't drag windows back and forth between screens "shared" in this way, I wanted a fast way to copy over some video files to watch on the PowerBook while I worked on the Mini.  So, basically, I had the Mac Mini and the PowerBook connected via FireWire across the Cinema Display, which was acting as a FireWire hub.  (It has a huge mega-connector for USB, Firewire, and DVI.)

Off of the other port on the Cinema Display FW Hub, I had a chain of four (now five) firewire drives, all mounted under the Mini before I even attempted this.  Basically, it's similar (as I understand it) to your connection between your WebSvr and your DBSvr, but there are 0 drives (other than the internal) hanging off the PowerBook and several hanging off of the Mini.

You can see the &lt;a href="http://www.astrogoth.com/~reeses/media/physical_layout.jpg"&gt;physical layout&lt;/a&gt; compared to the &lt;a href="http://www.astrogoth.com/~reeses/media/logical_view.jpg"&gt;logical view&lt;/a&gt;.

Yeah, it's gross, but it was giving me slightly higher throughput than my gig-E switch until I turned off a few other devices on the same switch (I was taxing the already weak switch).

What happened is that, after a while of using the machine, I suddenly noticed that one of the drives in that long drive chain was mounted under both the PowerBook and the Mini.  I had a nervous feeling about this that was confirmed when I noticed that neither machine could access the drive.

My problem would manifest itself in your environment, say, by the WebSvr mounting the DBSvr's firewire drive, or vice versa, unless I misunderstand your diagram.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-34" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-35</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="62.6.139.10" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>None@none.com</author>
      <description>Nice looking site. Pity ie7 has a problem with the top bar</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-35" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Pity you have to use a PC :)
But thanks for the heads up, this was a simple CSS fix.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-36" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="203.167.214.206" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>f1dinesh@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Very nice setup! looks great... I want one of those NOW ;)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-37" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.153.92.72" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jamesgrossjamesgross@gmailc.com</author>
      <description>Very nice article.  Not to sound like a fool, but what's the other piece of hardware you have in the system?  I'm referring to the two items sandwiched between the three minis.  I can't see any reference to it in the article...  (must be blind).  :)

- james</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-38" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-244-39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2006 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.153.92.72" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jamesgrossjamesgross@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Ok, I'm a blind fool.  found it.  haha.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="44-39" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Getting On Good Terms With The OS X Shell</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/3/19/getting-on-good-terms-with-the-os-x-shell</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="faec91b7d8897785eb02de9d59512c9f" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Getting On Good Terms With The OS X Shell</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 21:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-296-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.161.58.127" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>info@richard5.net</author>
      <description>Didn't know this iTerm application, I've been using it for a few days and I must say I really like it. Thanks...</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="96-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-296-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.227.190.98" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>dingoboard@mac.com</author>
      <description>This is a great start for shell NOOBs like me.  More please!  THANKS!!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="96-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-296-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.9.93.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I forgot about posting these. I recommend that you get used to putting in some personal aliases in the &lt;code&gt;~/.bash_profile&lt;/code&gt; file. For instance, here are a few. The first one adds a few arguments to the &lt;code&gt;ls&lt;/code&gt; command that shows more info by default and the second assumes that you have MySQL installed with a secure root password. This saves you from having to type this long line out all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;code type="sh"&gt;
# My Alias Shortcuts
alias ls="ls -la"
alias mysql="/usr/local/mysql/bin/mysql -u root -p"
&lt;/code&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can get the idea on how to add more. For instance, if you have a directory that you go to a lot, just pick an alias name like "blogroot" and add it here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="96-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>My Own Soup to Nuts Recipe for Ruby on Rails on OS X</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/5/29/my-own-soup-to-nuts-recipe-for-ruby-on-rails-on-os-x</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="530cbfee7e6d10bb9a28987a80c1ea84" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>My Own Soup to Nuts Recipe for Ruby on Rails on OS X</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 02:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2101-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2006 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="206.255.115.218" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>sam.bradley@mac.com</author>
      <description>Thank you for being so patient in your explanations.  I am intrigued by the topics of Ruby and Drupal.  I find your postings very interesting.  Thanks again.  Sam.....</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="101-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Web Service Woes</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2006/12/29/web-service-woes</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="4aecd9b5018379c7d894b6194e053a2a" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Web Service Woes</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2006 19:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2113-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2006 19:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="124.77.8.240" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>allensnoog@yahoo.com</author>
      <description>Under mac, there need some useful tool, such as  &lt;a href="http://www.softsea.com/review/XML-Transmitter.html"&gt;xml transmitter&lt;/a&gt; under windows, it is designed to POST or GET XML and SOAP messages via HTTP, SOAP and ftp protocol to a web server. this funtion should be helpful.

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="113-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Autotest Playlist For Red/Green Feedback</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/4/6/autotest-playlist-for-red-green-feedback</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="4957c8f43dfdd6e98fcb7eca1316705d" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Autotest Playlist For Red/Green Feedback</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:11:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2127-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.10.122.118" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>mike@huikau.com</author>
      <description>Very nice Ken!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="127-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2127-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Thanks Mike! My first cut at this was just picking a file randomly to play from the list, but duplicates in a list of 20 or 30 red sounds was bugging me. Since autotest is not a script but just constantly runs, it was easy to hack in a class attribute that kept the state of the index.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="127-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2127-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="99.167.103.194" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>rko618@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hi Ken,

Sweet upgrade. I'm really enjoying the autotest + sound.

I just wanted to mention that I do not believe require 'active_support' is necessary in the playlist.rb script. I removed it out and it seems to be working still.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="127-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2127-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Awesome! Thanks for letting me know.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="127-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>How to use Passenger (mod_rails) with rails edge 2.1</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/4/22/how-to-use-passenger-mod_rails-with-rails-edge-2-1</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="0bd5b96449a00b0bc6f5a4b98ed6c0ac" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>How to use Passenger (mod_rails) with rails edge 2.1</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 03:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2131-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="62.195.225.81" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>hongli@phusion.nl</author>
      <description>This problem has been fixed in the latest edge Rails.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="131-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2131-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2008 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Wow... thanks for commenting. I was talking to Mark Imbriaco last night and he was pointing me to the places where he saw the patches too. I updated my post so people get the right info. Kudos!
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="131-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>The "AJAX Head" Design Pattern</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/5/24/the-ajax-head-br-design-pattern</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="12ec65249e959c116b56daf8fef9d01b" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>The "AJAX Head" Design Pattern</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="59.178.61.155" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>rohandey@gmail.com</author>
      <description>what a great effort.. I liked your spirit to try and go for complete unobtrusive even with forms even when rails provide easy remote_form_for. Not sure if I will ever go for complete unobtrusiveness but a great lessons to learn reading this writeup</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you very much for the comment. So far the pattern is proving to be a big time saver. Although it really does relay on the fact that you can pick up the controller slack in your own JS classes. For, instance, I'm working on the ColumnsController#new action. All lines commented out will go away and be client side JS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table class="CodeRay"&gt;&lt;tr&gt;
  &lt;td class="line_numbers" title="click to toggle" onclick="with (this.firstChild.style) { display = (display == '') ? 'none' : '' }"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;1&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;2&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;3&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;4&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;6&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;7&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;8&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;9&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;11&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;12&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;13&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;14&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;td class="code"&gt;&lt;pre ondblclick="with (this.style) { overflow = (overflow == 'auto' || overflow == '') ? 'visible' : 'auto' }"&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;span class="r"&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="fu"&gt;new&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  current_user.columns.create!&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  head &lt;span class="sy"&gt;:ok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;# @remove_welcome = true if (@user.columns.length == 1)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;# render :update do |page|&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.remove :welcome_box if @remove_welcome&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.insert_html :top, 'col_wrapper', {:partial =&amp;gt; 'new_col', :locals =&amp;gt; {:col =&amp;gt; @column}}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.visual_effect :pulsate, &amp;quot;col_#{@column.id}&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.reorder_then_create_box_sortables(@column,@user)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.create_column_sortable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;#   page.make_msg('good','Column created.')&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;  &lt;span class="c"&gt;# end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;span class="r"&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;tt&gt;
&lt;/tt&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;




</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.37.186.207" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>mike.nicholaides@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hey! I've actually been thinking about this design pattern for a couple weeks, and I'd really like to hear more in the future how it works out, especially in terms of maintainability and testability.

Great article!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.63.103.84" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>casey.rosenthal@port49.com</author>
      <description>That is not a design pattern.

Essentially you are moving the controller to the client, which is a Remote Evaluation architecture style.  What you describe is a fine idea, but it is an implementation, not a pattern.

Thanks!
-CLR</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.102" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@CLR Agreed :)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.151.46.39" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>esconsult1@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Its a good idea for certain kinds of sites (intranets, highly dynamic content, etc).

However, its impractical for public-facing sites, since people would never be able to deeply find you in the search engines.

I searched this page for the word "degrade" (and variants), and nothing came up. No degradation at all.

Good idea in some minimal instances where content is not required to be indexed, bad idea for most public use-cases.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Ericson Smith - Yea I totally agree, but I think that is a moot point. First, remember that I am talking about the HomeMarks site and the latest version, not yet deployed.

Second, consider that every page on the public facing site, even those with AJAX forms that follow this implementation are behind a GET request. All the page updates, like form errors, user input would never be seen by a bot anyway. Remember bots do not do forms and they REALLY do not do anything AJAX or non GET, like POST/PUT/DELETE in the restful sense. </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="139.6.221.106" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>This truly sounds nice and I definitely need more experience with unobtrusive JavaScript. I like this idea very much and your approach looks promising. But I have two issues:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 1. You want to abandon inline RJS which I can fully understand. It is ugly and spoils your controller code. But you can use dedicated RJS templates. Which will need still a lot of work to be totally unobtrusive I think. But you still have the power to use dynamic creation of JavaScript code, depending on the context.&lt;br /&gt;
 2. The second issue I have is somewhat related to the first. Due to the fact that you relocate all your interaction logic including the required content to the client side you lose any chance to have localization or internationalization. Which is crucial for bigger sides. But I think one could address this issue with the first one.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Anyway, this was a great article which I had fun to read.
&lt;br /&gt;
Keep up the good work.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Dirk About #1, I really thought hard about trying to keep RJS, even in separate files, but it is really really hard to stay object oriented when using RJS. It really is a very procedural way of issuing JS commands. About the best OO way of using RJS is to drop down to the page&lt;&lt; command and just dump raw JavaScript commands that you know their exists an object for. Something like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
page.&lt;&lt; "HmSite.flash('good','Message');"
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But once you start doing that you might as well totally decouple and just stay full OO in the view land&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the localization, yea, I hear ya. The good thing is that this might not be that hard. Consider that all object errors still come from the app via JSON, there could be some helper that works in tandem with the rescue_from controller action so the array of error messages gets localized. So that solves the problem for errors and of course all GET requests can render localized content like a rails app normal would. That just leaves the simple flash messages generated by JavaScript, which are few. I'm sure there would be an easy JS way of telling which language the browser wants and then changing that string?&lt;/p&gt; </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="99.147.76.43" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>braynsray@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hey Ken ... first off: great article. There's a lot of good ideas and great example code.

Second: I've often struggled with this implementation, due to a few concerns:

1. 
I'm not a huge fan of Javascript and I admit this is probably just my lack of knowledge in that arena, but debugging javascript has always been a major pain in the ass. Yes, Firebug helps relieve that pain, but I still cringe when I have to go in and much around with things.

2.
This approach is *so* javascript intensive. Look at all the code you've had to write for a simple form submission. 

3.
The unobtrusive approach, in my opinion, tends to lead to unnecessariliy 'hidden' (unobtrusive, obviously) functionality. Which is fine, I think, as long as a great deal of caution is taken to point future developers in the right direction.

For instance ... when a new developer comes on and looks at the views and sees a simple "form_for" and then goes to look at the rendered result and finds that the form is actually not a simple form submission ... she is now forced to go dig through javascript to locate how the unobtrusive javascript is being attached. This functionality could be 'hidden' just about anywhere.

Anyways ... don't mean to degrade your article by any means. It's a great read and I will definitely give some of your implementations a try.

Best Regards.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2136-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2008 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="99.147.76.43" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>braynsray@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey Ken ... first off: great article. There's a lot of good ideas and great example code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second: I've often struggled with this implementation, due to a few concerns:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm not a huge fan of Javascript and I admit this is probably just my lack of knowledge in that arena, but debugging javascript has always been a major pain in the ass. Yes, Firebug helps relieve that pain, but I still cringe when I have to go in and much around with things.

&lt;p&gt;This approach is *so* javascript intensive. Look at all the code you've had to write for a simple form submission. 

&lt;p&gt;The unobtrusive approach, in my opinion, tends to lead to unnecessariliy 'hidden' (unobtrusive, obviously) functionality. Which is fine, I think, as long as a great deal of caution is taken to point future developers in the right direction.

&lt;p&gt;For instance ... when a new developer comes on and looks at the views and sees a simple "form_for" and then goes to look at the rendered result and finds that the form is actually not a simple form submission ... she is now forced to go dig through javascript to locate how the unobtrusive javascript is being attached. This functionality could be 'hidden' just about anywhere.

&lt;p&gt;Anyways ... don't mean to degrade your article by any means. It's a great read and I will definitely give some of your implementations a try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Regards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="136-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Coulda Shoulda Woulda</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/5/30/coulda-shoulda-woulda</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="a909c78a10d85a2d272391e7004c2430" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Coulda Shoulda Woulda</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 03:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2147-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adding my own addition here. I have found that the "should_require_login" method should have a logout at the top of the method. So like this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
    def should_require_login(*actions)
      actions.each do |action|
        should "Require login for '#{action}' action" do
          logout
          get(action)
          assert_redirected_to(login_url)
        end
      end
    end
&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My logout method looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;
    def logout
      @request.reset_session
    end
&lt;/pre&gt;

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="147-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2147-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.90.37.117" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>don@dream-in-color.net</author>
      <description>I'm trying to find your Omnigraffle template for Ruby Databases... can you point me to a download link?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="147-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2147-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2008 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Sadly I could not find that from any of my backups. It somehow got lost in the move from Drupal to Mephisto. Sorry!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="147-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Stop Exception Notifications With The ZombieShotgun</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/7/6/stop-exception-notifications-with-the-zombieshotgun</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="92c8088a1f9f789671198898732293ad" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Stop Exception Notifications With The ZombieShotgun</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>One thing to note, If you use this for pre rails 2.1, then you will have to return a false in the shoot_zombies method so it will stop the filter chain. I believe rails 2.1 now assumes that any render or redirect stops the filter chain now.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="62.195.225.81" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>hongli@phusion.nl</author>
      <description>Better turn ZOMBIE_ATTACK_DIRS into a Set. Array#include?() takes linear time while Set#include?() takes constant time in the average case.

ZOMBIE_AGENTS should also be turned into a single regular expression.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Hongli I totally agree! I have not done a double take on this code in well over a year or two, when I was new to programming altogether. The optimizations / best practices I'll leave to those that choose to use this and test it :) Thanks for hanging out and commenting on my blog!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.182.186.100" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>justin.marney@viget.com</author>
      <description>According to http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Zombie_Survival_Guide a shotgun, while seemingly effective, might get you in trouble when you run out of shells.  It is worth remembering that any infection outbreak has the potential to last years.  Sustainability is key.  I've heard that a http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coa_de_jima is one of the best tools for the job.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="208.124.190.170" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>wesley.moxam@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I tried dealing with this issue too, by routing requests that were using the OPTIONS http verb. I wrote about it here: http://rails.learnhub.com/lesson/page/2329-dealing-with-microsoft-office-protocol-discovery-in-rails

That solution didn't work so well, as it ended up matching on incorrect urls, thus sending me an exception notification every time there was a 404.
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="90.151.144.237" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>rene.dekart@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I think it's better to stop such requests with your proxy server or load balancing software. Nginx, Apache, Lighttpd, or any other stuff that proxies requests to application servers. In this case zombues will not abuse your application.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.8.245.10" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bhauff@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I have experienced some exceptions being thrown by the 'Microsoft Data Access Internet Publishing Provider Protocol Discovery' user agent trying to use the http method OPTIONS.  So I added a method to Zombie Shotgun to handle this:

&lt;pre&gt;
def zombie_method_attack?
  rm = request.env["REQUEST_METHOD"].downcase.to_sym
  !ActionController::Routing::HTTP_METHODS.include? rm
end
&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@brandon Very cool. BTW, the rails request object has a request.method method :)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2163-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2008 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.8.245.10" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bhauff@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for the feedback Ken.  I think the Zombie Shotgun could be packaged up and placed on GitHub.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="163-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Hell'OO HomeMarks</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/8/18/in-hell-oo-for-homemarks</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="b6d100759f65a8c40a5d25ae4561d825" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Hell'OO HomeMarks</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 01:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2172-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 01:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="210.56.88.54" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>drnicwilliams@gmail.com</author>
      <description>For JavaScript unit testing perhaps look at http://jsunittest.com (which is a rewrite of the unit test library used by prototypejs internally but without any prototypejs dependencies) and http://newjs.rubyforge.org which is a gem that includes a javascript_test rails generator (script/generate javascript_test some_js_file_to_test).  I think I have a blog post of running the js tests via a script/js_autotest which makes it a much nicer process.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="172-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2172-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 01:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Thanks a lot Dr Nic! I will take a look at those libs tonight.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="172-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2172-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 01:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="79.137.122.217" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ggast@sitek.it</author>
      <description>Hello ,

We are interested to migrate in Ruby ours websites and to start a socialnetwork around our marine system project. HomeMarks seem to me very well done but we have no expereience on Ruby. Our experience it's on Java , Javascript , Lotusdomino..

We are looking to some help to start Ruby inside our team implementing togheter some application.

By the way..our marine system is the integration of boat control , entertinement , internet connections for people like to work sailing.
the sytem is Mac based . Your experience on clustering is very interesting .
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="172-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Going Horizontal On The Multicade</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/9/14/going-horizontal-on-the-multicade</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="21e913f795f0e201018027174bc0c486" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Going Horizontal On The Multicade</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 18:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2190-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="65.242.94.194" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>skhisma@gmail.com</author>
      <description>And nearly killing your old multicade board in the process!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="190-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Using Autotest For Rails Plugin Development</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/9/19/using-autotest-for-rails-plugin-development</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="39cd59d88bbce17c7dd0177ec06ce8a2" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Using Autotest For Rails Plugin Development</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 17:46:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2194-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2008 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="84.9.147.52" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jamie@thelucid.com</author>
      <description>I use a simpler, yet not quite as flexible approach outlined here: http://www.thelucid.com/articles/2007/07/24/using-autotest-when-developing-rails-plugins</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="194-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Code-O-Lanterns: What Scares You?</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2008/10/13/code-o-lanterns-what-scares-you</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="85bc07063d2761ca8efe3819e2e89526" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Code-O-Lanterns: What Scares You?</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:52:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2214-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As an aside... here is they way to take screen shots of you OS X screen saver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre class="command"&gt;
sleep 4 ; screencapture -m ~/desktop/ss.png
&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="214-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2214-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="132.194.34.70" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ajaswa@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Very cool Ken. I'm guessing they don't have a windows ver?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="214-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2214-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@andrew Not that I know of.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="214-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2214-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2008 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="96.228.135.93" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>mwhuss@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Excellent, finally changed my default leopard background.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="214-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>MultiRuby The MacPorts Way. Testing Your Rails Apps With Ruby 1.9</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2009/1/20/multiruby-the-macports-way-testing-your-rails-apps-with-ruby-1-9</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="c787bd9362c0c88b7c8377401e9f4d3f" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>MultiRuby The MacPorts Way. Testing Your Rails Apps With Ruby 1.9</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 04:19:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2243-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2009 04:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.190.41.56" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>laconia@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Nice article. It really helped me. I would suggest one change to your "chruby" subroutine. Instead of this line, 

for i in $rubyexes; do

I would use this:

for i in ${rubyexes[*]}; do

using that bash array syntax is more universal and worked for GNU bash, version 3.2.17(1)-release (i386-apple-darwin9.0)
Copyright (C) 2005 Free Software Foundation, Inc.

Many thanks!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="243-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>PDF::Writer For Ruby 1.9</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2009/5/14/pdf-writer-for-ruby-1-9</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="455769dd6de315033676e23b86afe721" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>PDF::Writer For Ruby 1.9</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 13:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2281-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Just an additional note, this gem of pdf-writer is 1.8.7 and 1.9.1 compatible. It will not work under 1.8.6 as it does not have transitional code/methods in place.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="281-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2281-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2009 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="89.28.14.35" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>garykp@ds4ns1ns2.cn</author>
      <description>Hi. I like the way you write. Will you post some more articles?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="281-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Visor Terminal on Snow Leopard</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2009/8/18/visor-terminal-on-snow-leopard</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="5d42d15d0af7c246fb1d837b4bef6932" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Visor Terminal on Snow Leopard</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="69.27.141.38" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>luhkiee@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Amazing! Thanks so much, it's such a good idea -- I can't believe I didn't think of it. I've been dying to get my visor back.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>No problem! I took a good few hours out of my day last week to get this done and I'm glad others are finding it useful.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="69.113.211.49" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>coneybeare@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for this!  I have been dying without it since WWDC.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.94.235.164" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tanja@itendswith.com</author>
      <description>There's an easier way: go to Applications -&gt; Utilities, do a 'get info' on Terminal.app (or press &#226;&#338;&#732;-i) and check 'Open in 32-bit mode'. Start Terminal.app.
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="213.196.189.197" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>noreply@skatepark-weinfelden.ch</author>
      <description>@tanja, this way does not work 100%. terminal is starting (incl. visor) but i see no window.... do you know something about that problem?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Tanja yea... but your missing the point. This solution creates a separate app that does two important things. (1) You do not have to force your primary terminal app to be 32-bit. (2) You can have a visor terminal that seems part of the core OS by not having a dock icon, etc and can be launched in the background on login. Much much cleaner IMHO.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="77.4.182.209" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Thanks a lot. Works perfect for me with Snow Leopard. :-)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.94.235.164" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tanja@itendswith.com</author>
      <description>@Ken: ah, you're absolutely right!  I did miss those excellent points, at first. I do like your approach more in terms of cleanliness.  I especially like the missing dock icon, it's not like I don't already have 20 or so of them *cough*.

Thanks for your solution!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.70.108.74" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>cwilliams@allancraig.net</author>
      <description>@Ken - Thanks so much for posting this! Very elegant implementation. Love it!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.25.253.53" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>This might be easier: http://aralbalkan.com/2366 

In short, run Terminal in 32bit mode and Visor should work.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="93.183.250.147" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>kislo.metal@gmail.com</author>
      <description>please, could you describe how to change font size, etc. </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="99.2.138.121" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>chiphayner@gmail.com</author>
      <description>How do you edit the colors of the new visor terminal window? I'm used to the white-on-black that I have with my other terminal, and would like to get those back.  I can't find any preferences area to change these after using the directions above.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-11" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="99.2.138.121" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>chiphayner@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Ahhh.... nevermind.  I changed the LSUIElement value to "0" temporarily to allow me to select the app itself, made the changes, and swapped it back to "1".

One thing to note -- you will have to close the app through the activity monitor (or something similar) in order to restart it after making this settings change, as there is no easy way to close the program when LSUIElement is set to 1.

Great work, Ken!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-12" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.188.125.248" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>glenn@glennfu.com</author>
      <description>The VisorTerminal.app you provide zipped works great, but it doesn't have the split-pane feature of the new Terminal.app, and is twice the size of the original.  I tried following your instructions to create a new one, but the steps didn't work for me.  I'm guessing the Terminal.app you worked with was slightly different since you made it on the 18th and not after SL was released on the 28th.  Have you found a way to do this again with the latest release?
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-13" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-14</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Chip The easiest way to edit preferences for the VisorTerminal is to just bring it into scope, open it and click on it, then hit Command-,. That is "Command" plus "comma". That's the default keyboard shortcut for any Mac app's preferences. I have found that I even have to edit the "columns" to match my monitor width.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;@Glenn The VisorTerminal that I have provided for download is the Terminal.app from "Leopard" not "Snow Leopard". The reason for that is so that you have the 32-bit compatibility. Yea, I've heard you can make your 64-bt "Snow Leopard" terminal 32-bit too. But I've already described why I do not like that. If your keen on the split pane, etc or features only available in the Snow Leopard's Terminal.app, then you may have to find a different solution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-14" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="97.104.249.64" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>mike@mailinator.com</author>
      <description>Hey this is a great article and thank you very much for the download and exact plist copy. Definitely saved me a bunch of time.

I know visor is visor and a replacement is hard to find but the great app Dterm has now become free and works under snow leopard. The app was updated and made free for snow leopard. I am using your method so thank you!! Still Dterm is a good solution. 

http://www.decimus.net/dterm.php</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-15" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="203.59.215.175" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>aaronmaras@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Brilliant, works like a charm. Wish I'd had Visor set up like this months ago</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-16" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.195.208.138" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>*Almost* works perfectly for me.  I can't get it to actually give VisorTerminal.app focus, so I can't change the preferences (like the background and fonts and such).  Even if I look in the list of running programs via Force Quit, it's not there.

Any ideas?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-17" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Sergey I covered this already, to give VisorTerminal focus so you can hit the Command-Comma keyboard shortcut, just bring it into view like any other app (or use the toolbar icon "show visor") and hit the keyboard shortcut. Remember, you will never see VisorTerminal in your dock normal app list (my preferred implementation) but just trust the fact that if you have it in front of you, and you click on the window and hit Command-Comma, you will get the prefs window.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-18" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="208.184.6.27" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>www.superarts.org@na.com</author>
      <description>My Visor always crashes on since I've updated it to 1.9.1, on either Leopard and Snow Leopard. 1.5 is much more stable but on Leopard it does not look right (cannot cover the whole screen). Have you guys experiencing similar crash problem, and how you avoid it? Thanks in advance.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-19" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="208.184.6.27" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>www.superarts.org@na.com</author>
      <description>I mean "1.5 does not look correctly on Snow Leopard", not Leopard. I've tried to disable both effects and it does nothing, FYI.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-20" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-21</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="127.0.0.1" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>afrajag@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I just copy the Terminal.app to VisorTerminal.app and make VisorTerminal (Get Info) to run in 32-bit mode. Now visor works fine.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-21" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.25.130.156" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tradyblix@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I'm having the 1.9.1 crashing (on Leopard) and so is a friend. So you're not alone. After reading this article, pondering the behavior on Leopard, and discovering the split screen functionality, I'm thinking I'm going to give Visor a miss until they fix those things and it works with the 64 bit SL terminal natively. I just don't want to do hacks on my super fast new install just yet. Sigh.

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-22" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-23</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="74.94.66.171" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>blair@datapro.net</author>
      <description>Worked great for me!

Before doing this, you should go to ~/Library/Preferences and copy com.apple.Terminal.plist to com.apple.VisorTerminal.plist so your new VisorTerminal retains your settings.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-23" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="134.197.100.184" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>niczak@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Worked like a charm.  @Rapotor007's comment (copy ~/Library/Preferences/com.apple.Terminal.plist to com.apple.VisorTerminal.plis) was also very helpful.  </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-24" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="66.188.125.248" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>glenn@glennfu.com</author>
      <description>I'm also getting the crashes all too frequently now.  You said there was trouble getting the new version to work because it's 64bit, but my processor actually doesn't support 64bit so all my stuff is 32.  I don't have the option to toggled to anything after clicking Get Info like described by others.  Is there something else I can try to get my Snow Leopard terminal working with Visor?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-25" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Glenn, this article is all about getting the old "Leopard" version of terminal working as the VisorTerminal in "Snow Leopard". IE, using a 32-bit app that is known to work for SIMBL/Visor and changing it a bit for what I call usability. Did you make sure to follow all the directions and download the supplied app?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-26" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="158.109.1.9" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>piscue@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks so much! I was addicted to visor on leopard</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-27" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="207.118.171.139" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>david@whatcould.com</author>
      <description>Thanks Ken, this is terrific.

@Sergey and others who had trouble setting the fonts, colors, etc, in the preferences -- I had the same issue. Command-comma just didn't do anything, and I couldn't make VisorTerminal take focus (I had the Visor menubar icon disabled.)

The trick: enable Visor, and hit Command-N to get a new terminal window. For some reason this enables Command-comma, and you can edit the font, etc for the visor window.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-28" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="77.87.158.254" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>rakoth.lichlord@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I'm getting odd results with this: with LSUIElement=1 the app launches but does not react to the key, and Visor icon is not present in the toolbar - as if the bundle was not loaded into the app.
With LSUIElement=0 it works, but on launch it opens a usual window with Visor settings and the Visor icon in menubar is grey; to get drop-down console window I have to close this one and open another - then Visor icon in menubar highlights, and console opens on key press.
I use SIMBL 0.9.1b and Visor 2.0.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-29" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="88.146.67.141" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>antonin@hildebrand.cz</author>
      <description>Yuriy: You are using a brand new SIMBL beta. Injection mechanism changed and Visor bundle is injected into Terminal.app slightly after launch. That is why visor does not capture the first window being opened.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-30" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.86.119.224" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bawigga@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I saw the same thing as Yuriy... Antonin was correct. I had the beta simbl installed and it was causing problems with visor. Installing the leopard/tiger version fixed it.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-31" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-32</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="216.252.73.12" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>matth+metaskills@mlalonde.net</author>
      <description>I tried this with the current version (2.1) of SL Terminal.app, it works great. However visor won't load when I set LSUIElement to 1, and even when I don't, Terminal.app won't open Visor as the default window. Any ideas?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-32" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-33</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.80.113.127" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ben@lifeofreilly.org</author>
      <description>I actually found that it was easier to use a copy of Terminal.app (named VisorTerminal.app). I have it set to run in 32-bit mode, but then if there are any new features to Terminal, VisorTerminal will have them, too.

Plus, I was having strange errors with the Visor with the VisorTerminal you provided. Every time I opened the visor, the last line visible would be removed and the cursor would appear in the middle of the visor window.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-33" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="72.94.179.78" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>mdeltito@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I too am seeing strange behavior with both a Leopard VisorTerminal and a Snow Leopard modified VisorTerminal. Ben R put it best:

"Every time I opened the visor, the last line visible would be removed and the cursor would appear in the middle of the visor window."

Any idea on how to fix this? I thought that doing what Ben did would fix the issue, but I'm still having trouble</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-34" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-35</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="204.181.64.4" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Visor 2.1 was just released. It works in 64-bit mode with SIMBL 0.9.x, and it seems to correct that problem with the lines disappearing and the cursor jumping around.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-35" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-36</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.90.9.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bmorgenthaler@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Running SL in 32bit and I still can't get this to work.  I have downloaded the latest versions of Visor and SIMBL and copied my Terminal.app to create VisorTerminal.app.  Everything works great until I go to make it autolaunch and hide from the dock, once I place the LSUIElement entry into Info.plist Visor no longer recognizes VisorTerminal.app and the program launches as a normal terminal window sans dock and menubar.  I remove the LSUIElement entry and try launching it again and it still doesn't function and won't until I restart my laptop.

Anyone have similar issues or ideas on how to fix it?  I really would love Visor, I've become addicted to yakuake on my linux box and keep hitting the hot keys for it :-D</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-36" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-37</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Brenden &lt;strong&gt;UPDATE: Hacks no longer needed, latest Visor/SIMBL is 64-bit Snow Leopard happy!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-37" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.90.9.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bmorgenthaler@gmail.com</author>
      <description>@Ken No hacks needed to get it to run or to get the hidden terminal?  I have it running against Terminal.app just fine but it's not hidden and so I always have the app sitting in the dock.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-38" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-39</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Brenden Depends on what you want. I myself have terminal windows open outside my visor terminal. Because of that, I do not mind having the icon in my dock. However, I have confirmed that if you want to, you can open up the Terminal.app that comes with Snow Leopard and add the LSUIElement to 1 and it will still work.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-39" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="130.83.148.142" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>@Brenden: I can confirm the odd behaviour of setting LSUIElement to 1 with the current versions of Visor.bundle and SIMBL in Snow Leopard. Tried it with both Leopard's Terminal as well as with SL's, no way of getting to work just yet without the icon/active menu :/</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-40" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="12.51.35.162" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>antonin@hildebrand.cz</author>
      <description>LSUIElement issue is explained here: http://github.com/darwin/visor/issues/closed/#issue/32

In short: it is new SIMBL 0.9.x feature and the only way how to get working hidden Terminal.app is to use SIMBL 0.8.x and LSUIElement=1 with Terminal.app forced to 32-bit mode.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-41" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.70.108.74" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>cwilliams@allancraig.net</author>
      <description>You can use AppleScript to inject the 64 bit SIMBL into Terminal with the LSUIElement set to 1. Save this as an application and include it in your startup items.

tell application "Terminal"
	inject SIMBL into Snow Leopard
end tell</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-42" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="59.162.86.164" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>pathsny@gmail.com</author>
      <description>The comments here have been fantastic. I've finally got visor working on startup with the leapord terminal. But I'm still unable to make it larger than the fixed 20 rows. Anyone else figured it out?
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-43" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="213.100.24.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>matts.bengtzen@gmail.com</author>
      <description>@Craig Williams I can confirm your method works great! Thanks for posting it, really helped me out. 

I love having the terminal hidden from the dock, but still available through Visor! I waited so long since Snow Leopard was released, but finally! Yeay!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-44" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2288-45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2009 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="213.100.24.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>matts.bengtzen@gmail.com</author>
      <description>@path You can set the size of the window by modifying the number of visible rows of the "visor"-profile. When terminal-visor is visible, type apple+comma-sign simultaneous to bring up the preferences. Navigate to Settings, and choose the "Visor"-profile. There you can edit the rows-textbox!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="288-45" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>The Ultimate OS X Snow Leopard Stack For Rails Development - x86_64, MacPorts, Ruby 1.8/1.9, SQL Server, SQLite3, MySQL &amp; More</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2009/9/5/the-ultimate-os-x-snow-leopard-stack-for-rails-development-x86_64-macports-ruby-1-8-1-9-sql-server-more</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="46e814d1333c3d7c37cd9c95bfea7b99" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>The Ultimate OS X Snow Leopard Stack For Rails Development - x86_64, MacPorts, Ruby 1.8/1.9, SQL Server, SQLite3, MySQL &amp; More</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="117.102.33.19" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>myschizobuddy@gmail.com</author>
      <description>How about installing ruby dependencies via macports and then compile Ruby Enterprise Edition by Phusion.

Just for readers, You can use Porticus http://porticus.alittledrop.com/ its a gui frontend to Macports</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@MySchizoBuddy I'm sure you can do that and it is nice to know there is a MacPort GUI out there. Interesting, but GUI's are not my thing. I'm sure some will find it helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just updated the article with SQLite3 and MySQL directions. So hopefully others will find that useful too. Lastly, I have never needed REE in my development environment. The RAM savings just do not stack up as a needed thing for me but I'm sure what you suggest would work just fine :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="58.96.101.34" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>speistam@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thank you very much for the comprehensive write up!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="86.8.6.167" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>josh@enjoythespace.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for the guide its great, although I'm getting stuck at the first hurdle...

When installing ruby I'm getting this error:

---&gt;  Computing dependencies for ruby
---&gt;  Activating readline @6.0.000_1+darwin
Error: The following dependencies failed to build: readline
Error: Status 1 encountered during processing.


Any clues to why this is happening?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="74.136.134.7" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>dave.starke@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for this write up.  It works perfectly!</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="82.236.208.147" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>stephanparis@gmail.com</author>
      <description>almost working :)

tsql works

but isql gives me : [IM002][unixODBC][Driver Manager]Data source name not found

it's like it does not finds the proper odbc.ini file...

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="208.80.98.25" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>shashy_d@yahoo.ca</author>
      <description>tsql and isql work for me. iodbctest does not. I have odbc.ini and odbcinst.ini in /Library/ODBC. Where does freetds.conf have to be located?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
@Stephan &amp; @essdee, if you are using iODBC and anything outside of the &lt;code&gt;/opt&lt;/code&gt; directory, you have done something wrong. FreeTDS and especially the ruby ODBC binding want and prefer unixODBC. I think I made this point in my article too.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="84.2.215.250" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>feketeferenc@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hi, I've foudd and interesting problem. I've used the gems mentioned in the post with freetds to successfully connect to a legacy ms sgq database. After I've upgraded to snow leopard, get the following error when I try to conenct to the database:
Product.first
/Library/Ruby/Gems/1.8/gems/dbd-odbc-0.2.4/lib/dbd/odbc/statement.rb:41: [BUG] Bus Error
ruby 1.8.7 (2008-08-11 patchlevel 72) [universal-darwin10.0]

and exits from ruby shell. I've recompiled freetds with unixodbc, recompiled the neccessary gems but it doesn't help. I've recompiled the ruby-odbc bingings but still got errors. tsql -C says it's using the unixodbc. do you have any idea?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="98.166.1.121" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Azabaj That path for ruby is the Mac's ruby, not the ruby that should be installed via MacPorts into /opt/local/bin/ruby. Made sure you have your PATH setup correctly and have "everything" including ruby installed into the /opt dir and make sure your PATH ENV uses that dir.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="91.82.172.88" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>feketeferenc@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for your answer.

The fact is, I'm using the ruby shipped with leopard and everything was worked fine. After upgrading to snow leo, only the ruby-odbc was messed up (other gems are working fine.).

So, if I install ruby from the macports, then I should install rubygems and all the gems I use for that "ported-ruby" and that's what I would like to avoid. 

However, I've spent 1.5 days trying to figure out whats going on, so it doesn't matter spending another hour on rebuilding my ruyb env from macports if it's truly neccessary:) (no guarantee, I know)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Azabaj I love Mac! I love Ruby. Take my advice, do not try to mix the ruby that talks to SQL Server with your Mac's ruby. Trust me! Go into /opt and your life will be easier. Regardless of what worked before.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-11" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="78.92.26.72" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>feketeferenc@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I've installed ruby from ports, reinstalled the most improtant gems for that specific project and the ruby-odbc and it works:) Thank you, for your advice! Now, I'm going to install all the other gem for my other projects. </description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-12" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-13</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="63.119.36.36" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tthibodeau@openlinksw.com</author>
      <description>I'm curious to learn whether the iODBC update for Snow Leopard resolves the issues you had with it.  

http://www.iodbc.org/dataspace/iodbc/wiki/iODBC/Downloads

I don't know why you say that RubyODBC prefers unixODBC, when there's no such note anywhere in the RubyODBC docs -- http://ch-werner.de/rubyodbc/ -- and indeed there is more mention of iODBC than unixODBC....

Similarly, what's the basis for your declaration that FreeTDS prefers unixODBC?

I'm somewhat disturbed by your creation of new files at /opt/local/etc/{odbc.ini,odbcinst.ini}.  This seems very likely to lead to confusion over time.  Why not make these links (hard or soft) to the pre-existing /Library/ODBC/{odbc.ini,odbcinst.ini} (recommended, System DSNs and ODBC settings) or ~/Library/ODBC/{odbc.ini,odbcinst.ini} (User DSNs and ODBC settings)?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-13" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-14</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
@Ted I was mistaken about FreeTDS not liking iODBC. I was quoting from memory and after looking again, I found the reason. It is in DBI's ODBC DBD. The below comment is from that source. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
 # Requires DBI and the 'ruby-odbc' package to work, and unixodbc (iodbc # WILL NOT WORK).
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
About your comment on the creation of opt's own odbc.ini and odbcinst.ini to match the MacPort unixODBC install. I do not see anything disturbing about this. Especially since the point of my directions is to stay away from mixing default Mac components.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Like I said to @Azabaj, I love Mac, but this stack is fraught with hidden dangers that newcomers to ruby/rails or users installing from source may not be aware of. If you have the skill, do what you want and feel is right, run the tests and educate us all. Cheers, Ken.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-14" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.18.246.240" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tom@themolehill.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for the great detail!  I followed and understood most everything!  Unfortunately, when I launch IRB and try to load a record I get the following error:

DBI::DatabaseError: IM002 (0) [iODBC][Driver Manager]Data source name not found and no default driver specified. Driver could not be loaded

I'm not sure why it is using iODBC?  If I run tsql -C, it shows iodbc NO and unixODBC YES?

Where should I be looking?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-15" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Tom We talked on IM about this... but what happened is that you had your /opt/local/bin and /opt/local/sbin at the end of your path vs the beginning.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-16" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="63.119.36.36" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tthibodeau@openlinksw.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Ken - Can we connect by email or IM or something?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I very much don't understand the motivation to avoid using default components on any OS, nor the preference to install redundant packages for the same task, whether different versions or entirely different packages ... but I hope that you will help us get the default stack working properly, whether or not you then choose to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'd especially like to at least get the non-native unixODBC vs Apple-chosen iODBC piece straightened out, even if you continue to prefer the build-from-source path to Ruby connection, over the install-pre-built path &lt;a href="http://odbc-rails.rubyforge.org/"&gt;we documented on RubyForge for the OpenLink ODBC Adapter for Ruby on Rails / Active Record&lt;/a&gt; and/or the &lt;a href="http://www.iodbc.org/dataspace/iodbc/wiki/iODBC/IODBCPerlHOWTO"&gt;DBD::ODBC build instructions on iODBC.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there's something not working in that default/native stack, we'd appreciate hearing directly about it, so we can work on getting it fixed, whether the issue lies in our own gear or one of the other packages.  Figuring out, writing up, and recommending workarounds just extends the life of such issues and increases confusion, benefiting no-one in the end.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-17" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-18</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.110" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>
&lt;p&gt;
  @Ted I see where you coming from but I still think you are missing my point. Let me walk you thru a series of examples and perspectives on where I am coming from so you can see my view. I certainly see your view and am not saying that yours is wrong or mine is better. We are just coming from different camps. If you have any feedback or want to talk on the side, my email can be found on the colophon/resume page here.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  First let's talk about your "workaround" theory. This is so not one of them! I did not come up with this stack because I had issues and needed to work around something in a black-box manner vs solving the real issue. As a matter of fact black-box hacking around is 100% against my nature. I choose to have ruby 1.8.7/1.9.1/REE/etc outside the Mac env because I like it. I like that my 1.8.7 is 15% faster than what is installed by Apple (your mileage may vary). I like not mixing things with their stuff for this particular stack because it suits me and is easy to do and seems to keep me upgrade worry free. I compare this to someone not linking "Preview.app" and just installing "Acrobat Reader". Both are there and both are usable and none is a workaround for the other. FYI, I prefer "Preview.app" :)
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Now about the other issue with the DBI's documented issue with iODBC. I've spent quite a bit of my time contributing to the SQL Server adapter code. In fact... it's not even fair to quantify it as contributing. I frankly assumed the project and wrote and maintain quite a bit of the code. Making that adapter run in 2000/2005/2008 in 2.x and in the upcoming 3.x rails is no small task. It is hard work and I have pushed changes and upstream patches when I find the time. I am in the middle of writing my first iPhone application and still maintain enough time to contribute to quite a few OSS projects. All that and still contributing my time to local Ruby/ObjC user groups. I pick my battles and do what I can and feel that I have done a great job so far.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  If you have love for iODBC and default components and the skill to contribute to those projects and hence after the fact the SQL Server adapter project, just do it. Now this is not a personal attack on you... but it is a peeve of mine that 95% of the people that contribute to the adapter or middle stack can not even run the tests or frankly care. They just say if I hacked this line it "works" and tell me to take that hack or leave it. This means that my love for my day job kicks in and I have to do it for them. Please do not fall into this category. If you want to help and advocate fixing something then just please do it. But please do not make the assumption that I am performing workarounds or that yours is the best only way. As software developers, we should know better.
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-18" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="212.202.139.154" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>doubledipthechip@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hello Ken,

first of all - thank you very much for this how-to. Actually, this was the first how-to ever that explained the connectivity to SQL Server correctly. I managed to get it working in minutes, as opposed to days like on Ubuntu. The SQL Server connectivity sure needs a lot of things sitting in the right place, doesn't it.

You saved me a lot of headaches. It would be great if you could maintain this how-to and update it should the need arise.

Also, what I would like to know is a convenient way to start and stop Apache and MySQL-Server in one go, through the command line. I would like to be able to stop my whole web development stack and free the resources. Right now I have Apache (from MacPorts) always "on" through launchctl.

Cheers
Bj&#195;&#182;rn</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-19" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Bjorn Thanks very much for the positive feedback. I do plan to keep this page updated and more importantly the wiki on the adapter's github site now has contributions on the stack for getting things up and running and that includes Ubuntu to. I published this article mainly to link from that wiki page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About the stop/start stuff. As most of my friends know, and joke me about, I have a huge profile. Since I use zsh and not bash, it's called my zshkit. Here are a few alias (works in bash too) that I have for managing some things.&lt;p&gt;

&lt;pre class="command"&gt;
# MySQL
alias my_stop="sudo launchctl stop org.macports.mysql5"
alias my_start="sudo launchctl start org.macports.mysql5"
alias my_rs="my_stop ; my_start"
alias myconf="mate /opt/local/etc/mysql5/my.cnf"
# Apache
alias apconf="mate /opt/local/apache2/conf ; sleep 1 ; mate /opt/local/apache2/conf/extra/httpd-vhosts.conf"
alias apstop="echo 'Stopping Apache2:' &amp;&amp; sudo apachectl stop"
alias apstart="echo 'Starting Apache2:' &amp;&amp; sudo -E apachectl start"
alias apr="apstop ; sleep 3 ; apstart"
&lt;/pre&gt;

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-20" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="93.164.3.6" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jacob@riff.dk</author>
      <description>Thanks for your walk-through. I am having some problems with ruby-odbc. I have compiled it with --with-odbc-dir=/usr/local/unixODBC-2.2.14/lib but when I run the test.rb file in the ruby-odbc folder, it still uses iODBC. Can you explain how ruby-odbc knows witch ODBC to use? 

Everything else is working perfectly.

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-21" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Jacob It sounds like your working against the grain of my article, perhaps you are using Homebrew? I ask because you have unixODBC in your /usr/local and not opt. If so, then you are running in the dependencies and crossed wires I ran into many times. Having ruby over here, this over there and that over yonder does not work well unless you really know what your doing. Without knowing your path, and where you decided to put your other parts, I'm no where near able to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps start over and do it all in opt?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-22" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="93.164.3.6" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jacob@riff.dk</author>
      <description>Thanks for your reply. I actually got it to work - I now have stock ruby, unixOBDC, freeTDS and ruby-odbc running on Snow Leopard. I can't believe the amount of hacking I had to do to make it work. 

I have made a blog post about it here: http://digitaljacob.riff.dk/?p=9

I hope that somebody can use it.

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-23" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="121.45.196.102" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>hugh@artpop.com.au</author>
      <description>I recently set up my new macbook and used Homebrew and RVM for all of this and it was a piece of cake. Best thing was I didn't have to make a single change to the underlying system.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I wrote a half-arsed article about it &lt;a href="http://hughevans.net/2009/11/05/homebrew-ruby-odbc"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but I really should write a full guide like yours because it is a great set up.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-24" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Hugh Good show, looks like HomeBrew has come around since I used it long ago. FYI, I have added your article under the adapters wiki page. Right now it is marked as untested. If you find the time, fire up the tests and let me know how it goes.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-25" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.15.117.0" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>christopher.joslyn@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I'm surprised you didn't need to set ARCHFLAGS when installing the mysql gem. Many other blogs recommend:
&lt;pre&gt;
sudo env ARCHFLAGS="-arch x86_64" \
gem install mysql -- --with-mysql-config=/opt/local/bin/mysql_config5
&lt;/pre&gt;

I had to do this on my machine or else I got &lt;code&gt;uninitialized constant MysqlCompat::MysqlRes&lt;/code&gt;. I think this issue is specific to version 2.8.1 of the gem. That might explain why you didn't run into this problem.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-26" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="174.103.214.198" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jonkinney@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for the guide Ken, I had some trouble with connecting up with FreeTDS because on a clean install of Snow Leopard the locale is set to us-ascii and not utf-8. I wrote up a quick blog post on how to modify os x's default locale to allow freetds to connect up to SQL Server.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="http://jonkinney.com/articles/2009/11/23/change-locale-on-os-x-snow-leopard-for-freetds-functionality"&gt;http://jonkinney.com/articles/2009/11/23/change-locale-on-os-x-snow-leopard-for-freetds-functionality&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks,&lt;br /&gt;
-Jon</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-27" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Jon Kinney Thanks! I just published your article on the SQL Server adapter wiki.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-28" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.41.21.78" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joshmckin@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Great tutorial. Got almost everything to working using MSSQL 2008, basic crud works fine, but tried to get active_record session store going and keep getting the following error: 

  DBI::DatabaseError: 22001 (8152) [unixODBC][FreeTDS][SQL Server]String or binary data would be truncated.: INSERT INTO [sessions] ([data], [created_at], [updated_at], [session_id]) VALUES('BAh7BjoQX2NzcmZfdG9rZW4iMVhWazJXb2ZOUzZiQTJpVDBXZ2ZuWEdOaTJp
QnRLRnprYnZKbzJiWGpxNzg9
', '2009-11-30 20:19:31.435', '2009-11-30 20:19:31.435', 'BAh7CDoQX2NzcmZfdG9rZW4iMVB2RCtuaVBtUUxLT3BrVEFtUExkSHphalpRd0xCQ2IxZE9rVDNadThSeTQ9Og9zZXNzaW9uX2lkIiU0ZDM1ZTI1NmU1MjQyMjM3NGZmMjY3MTU5NTFhZjk1NSIKZmxhc2hJQzonQWN0aW9uQ29udHJvbGxlcjo6Rmxhc2g6OkZsYXNoSGFzaHsABjoKQHVzZWR7AA==--49244d32c588044567f3458bed477038666bdbc9')


Double checked the fields in the db were the right data type and all looks good, any ideas what might be going wrong.

Thanks,</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-29" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.41.21.78" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joshmckin@gmail.com</author>
      <description>So it will work if I remove the session_id index, but this could be a problem when the app starts to see high traffic (which it will).
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-30" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-31</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="68.231.146.133" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jared.online@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Hey guys

Great post and lots of useful comments.  When trying to install MacPorts I'm getting:

Jareds-MacBook-Pro:~ jaredmcfarland$ sudo port install ruby
Password:
---&gt;  Computing dependencies for rubyError: Unable to execute port: can't read "build.cmd": Failed to locate 'make' in path: '/opt/local/bin:/opt/local/sbin:/bin:/sbin:/usr/bin:/usr/sbin' or at its MacPorts configuration time location, did you move it?


Any thoughts?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-31" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="86.179.34.208" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>william@geeksltd.co.uk</author>
      <description>Hey, that was interesting,

Keep up the good work,

Thanks for writing, most people don't bother.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-32" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.51" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;
@Josh Mckinney Your issue could be related to the data type. For instance, I think :text types might be varchar(max) in 2008 and you may need to force it to another type for the room to store serialized objects. I might recommend switching to the cookie store however I can help you debug this on the &lt;a href="http://groups.google.com/group/rails-sqlserver-adapter?hl=en" class="external-link"&gt;SQL Server Adapter Google Group&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
@Jared McFarland It looks like you have a PATH issue. If you have indeed already installed the Apple Developer Tools which are required, make sure you have added $PATH at the end of your /opt additions so that the your old paths are trailing at the end. Reverence the MacPort install page for the correct way to add the /opt stuff to you shell.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-33" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="71.41.21.78" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>joshmckin@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Ok have another issue that I think is more related to setup decribed above. For some reason I can change the database I am using for a test_app. My initial database was created from migrations just test the setup. Now I would like to use a different test database created using real world data from out existing system. Unfortunately despite all my efforts to change all the ODBC.ini file I could find a this my Mac and changing the database.yml when I start the start script/server or script/console rails continues to query the old database. I have no idea what is happening. The fact rails is completely ignoring the database.yml file and why unixODBC is ignoring the updated ODBC.ini is a complete mystery. I even used the 'find' command ( find / -name odbc.ini) and changed every file i that was found to the desired setup and still no dice. Anything would help I can have idea where to look at this point. &lt;br /&gt;
Thanks</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-34" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2321-35</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2009 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Josh Mckinney: It is kind of confusing, but maybe if I share how my setup works, that might help. Aside from the normal adapter/mode/username/password parts of my database.yml file, I only have a dsn option for each rails env. I find that using DSN's allow my to easily abstract some dynamic aspects of managing that file and pushes all the details to the odbc.ini file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that file for each DSN that the database.yml is using, just make sure your "Servername" and "Database" are set correctly and you should be good to go. There is very little that can go wrong here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="321-35" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Authenticated S3 GETs For Private Objects Using Paperclip</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2009/11/23/authenticated-s3-gets-for-private-objects-using-paperclip</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="9cf2e53454458ac5d64ca35fecdc95f2" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Authenticated S3 GETs For Private Objects Using Paperclip</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2452-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="97.124.83.143" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>threadhead@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Damn, that is timely. Just started working on the same this morning. Especially like the Noop processor.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="452-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2452-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="97.124.83.143" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>threadhead@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Ken,
I have not tested extensively, but it appears that if you omit :styles =&gt; {} from has_attached_file, then paperclip will do no post processing. I tried it uploading some PDF files and XLS files and it throws no errors.

According to paperclip readme: "NOTE: Because processors operate by turning the original attachment into the styles, no processors will be run if there are no styles defined."

So maybe you don't need the Noop processor?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="452-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2452-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>@Karl You are entirely correct! I just tested this today. Thanks for the heads up.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="452-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2452-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="72.197.51.158" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>twalpole@gmail.com</author>
      <description>I find it easier to just add a paperclip interpolation in an intiializer

Paperclip.interpolates(:s3_authenticated_url) do |attachment, style|
    AWS::S3::S3Object.url_for(attachment.path(style), attachment.bucket_name, :use_ssl=&gt;true, :expires_in=&gt;3.minutes)
end

and then in the has_attached_file call use the options
:s3_permissions=&gt;'private',
:url=&gt;':s3_authenticated_url'</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="452-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2452-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2009 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="10.0.1.21" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FYI, I noticed &lt;a href="http://github.com/thoughtbot/paperclip/commit/808d295086a8d363e69daed1f57449164c0232e4" class="external-link"&gt;this commit in paperclip&lt;/a&gt; which has exact results as mine, but still does not use the host alias. I may get around to adding a patch soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="452-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Unobtrusive JS In Rails 3 With Prototype </title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/1/29/unobtrusive-js-in-rails-3-with-prototype</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="59684fb734125bfa143197061d550e9f" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Unobtrusive JS In Rails 3 With Prototype </description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="208.96.213.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>stephen.celis@gmail.com</author>
      <description>When edge Rails made the switch, it started generating "prototype.rails.js" and "jquery.rails.js" files which take care of this for you, just make sure to javascript_include_tag them.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Awesome! Let me check that out&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yup, I had to generate a rails project from edge to find this. Seems the generator is remote and searching source did not yield a hit, which is why I did not find it earlier. The prototype code written is really nice. Very very informative reading it too. Thanks&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="96.252.182.202" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>kuprishuz@gmail.com</author>
      <description>The UJS functionality is currently going under some restructuring, most existing functionality will be moved into a legacy plugin:
http://github.com/rails/prototype_legacy_helper

and the javascript libraries have been rewritten removing backwards compat (as the legacy plugin will maintain 2.3 support):
http://github.com/rails/jquery-ujs
http://github.com/rails/prototype-ujs

these are being changed in favor of a cleaner 3.0 api such as link_to @user, :remote =&gt; true, :method =&gt; :delete and form_for @user, :remote =&gt; true as opposed to the link_to_remote and remote_form_for

</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="95.42.102.22" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>RStankov@gmail.com</author>
      <description>You can try my Event.delegate prototype plugin ( http://gist.github.com/66568 ). And just do this:

document.observe('dom:loaded', function(){
  document.delegate('a[data-method=delete]', click', MyJsObject.linkToDelete);
});

this will use event delegation, and won't populate the page with event handlers. ( as a bonus it will handle dynamic adding / removing of a[date-method=delete] elements )</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2761-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>Wow, thanks! Always cool when people find it useful.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="761-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Synchronizing Core Data With Rails (3.0.0.pre)</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/2/12/synchronizing-core-data-with-rails-3-0-0-pre</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="61d4cc6916320f1ca7c010e7e2068969" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Synchronizing Core Data With Rails (3.0.0.pre)</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="78.5.97.228" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author></author>
      <description>Thanks for sharing</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="201.62.203.58" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>danielvlopes@areacriacoes.com.br</author>
      <description>Very cool content... Have you considered the idea to record a screencast with your presentation?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have. The local user groups will soon have the ability to record our talks. I will also be in Richmond on March 8th doing this talk for the local CocoaHeads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.101.111.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>shaynesweeney@me.com</author>
      <description>I want to start off telling you how awesome these slides are, even without audio I've been able to learn and use so much in building out my current project. Much Appreciated!

I do, have a few questions if you wouldn't mind answering! :)

The annotation at the top of slide 66 (Customize To Your API) reads:
  // Assumes MyRequest &amp; MyFormRequest subclasses of
  // ASIHTTPRequest and ASIHTTPFormRequest (minimal use).

I assume that ASIHTTPFormRequest is meant to be ASIFormDataRequest. I've created my subclasses, but they remain pretty empty as of now; simply namespacing ASI's classes.

Considering the note "minimal use", my question is: What kind of behavior have you added to these subclasses?


Later on slide 69 (Import On Launch) you implement the method "getUserDataFor:" in the ASIHTTPRequest category (MyAdditions). The next slide shows the success delegate method implementation of "didGetUserData:"; you check if the request response "isNotModified", conditionally modify an Etag and call import.

Questions are:

1) You mention that this is implemented in "The Controller" - is this referring to a subclass of UIViewController or are you using "other controllers" here?

2) You pass off the request to the application's delegate, regardless of the "isNotModified" condition - what does this method look like and what is it's purpose?

3) Would very much like to see an example of your import method implementation, where we actually "sync" with CoreData. I'm a bit fuzzy on how I'd implement maintaining the managed objects (existing, vs new).


Again, thanks so much for this and I apologize ahead of time as I understand these questions may have been answered during your live presentation.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Shayne Sweeney, thanks for the kudos. I'll see if I can answer your questions in order. First, yes, that was supposed to be ASIFormDataRequest and as of yet, I have no behavior in those classes, most everything is in ASIHTTPRequestAdditions. That said, if I had time to refactor, I could move over a lot of my category extensions to sub class implementations. In fact most can, this includes the new designated initializer, class utility and factory methods as well as instance extensions like - (BOOL)isSuccess and - (BOOL)isNotModified. In actuality, I am having a hard time recalling why I went with a category vs subclasses. In my app I always use MyRequest class factories, and let the verb make a call on the correct low level implementation of weather to instantiate a MyRequest or MyFormRequest, which the utility verb helpers do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always sub class controller and most of my requests very rarely have a controller as a delegate. Hence why my designated initializer has the default catch all of letting the app delegate handle delegation. The main reason is just to log, but you could take the "oh shit" approach of alerts, refreshing entire data with popping back to root view if something really bad happened. Most requests just send and forget, only new item requests specify a model NSManagedObject as the delegate and even in that case it reports back to the app delegate afterward for logging and "oh shit" handling :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My import is not a real big amount of code and it's simple for one reason. It kills everything in the DB and just reimports again. There is no such thing in my app as an object is here and not there. An average large user of HomeMarks has a JSON payload when gzipped of only 5K or so, getting all user data is really small when your web server and iPhone connections are set up right. I love that ASIHTTPRequest has the gzip function built in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.101.111.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>shaynesweeney@me.com</author>
      <description>Thanks! I really appreciate your response.
(What's the newline secret? I apologize for the lack of formatting, but the newlines didn't translate over well.)</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The magic of hand coded &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; tags. I dont think this poor old mephisto blog has automatic comment formatting support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="75.101.111.130" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>shaynesweeney@me.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt; Ken, Thanks for that! I'll be sure to keep that in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've been hard at work implementing Core Data into app, keeping a close eye on your presentation throughout. One of the improvisations I've made in importing data has me thinking "there has to be a better way".&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In dealing with managed objects with relationships how do you manage staying true to the @property definition, or do you through it out and write your own implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let's say I have a MyPlace managed object that has a relationship to a MyAddress managed object. Each place has one address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The JSON from the server returns places with an "address" : { ... } element. The [MyPlace newObject:attributes] method takes the once JSON, now NSDictionary and loops over the keys setting the appropriate values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you handle setting the nested objects? Is it possible to maintain @properties within your managed objects. I suppose you could put conditions in the newObject: method but seems like a maintenance tradeoff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks! PS - I hope to write a response to your slides based on my experience to increase the available information on this topic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2777-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2010 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I basically have one class method at the top of each managed object class that does all the work. So in my case if I import a column object (has_many :boxes) and there is a boxes value in the JSON, then i just pushes it further down to the HMBoxes managed object class method and so on down the chain to bookmarks. This keeps things nice and tidy and let's a top level class champion all of its associations. Easy to do in my case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing that might not have been apparent in my slides -- each of my managed object models has a remoteID property that stores the PK from the web app's DB. Obviously this is needed for remote actions. Another thing that was interesting was in my rails model, bookmarks are polymorphic owned. Meaning a Inbox, Trashbox, or Box of any id can have_many :bookmarks and when a bookmark moves that polymorphic association changes it's scope as well as position. Core Data is not like a DB we rails developers are used to, even tho it is SQLite on the backend. We have to let go and let it manage our relationships and keys. To map my polymorphic bookmarks in Core Data, I had to use a technique called FETCHED_PROPERTIES, which let's me reflect on the calling object to define properties as predicates definitions. Even tho Core Data is iPhone OS, 3.0, Apple only fixed the FETCHED_PROPERTIES technique in OS 3.1 (thanks to my bug report).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yea there is a lot of info to share in this area. I would love to see your slides and I'll link to them too if you let me know.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="777-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>TextMate Theme &amp; Key Bindings For Xcode</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/3/19/textmate-theme-key-bindings-for-xcode</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="bdb333cc145ba2726ac93b2464892ef3" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>TextMate Theme &amp; Key Bindings For Xcode</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 15:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2797-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="98.175.62.195" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>andy@ninthdivision.com</author>
      <description>Very nice... thanks.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="797-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2797-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.90.13.43" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>krunk7+blog@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for this, got me most of the way there...now to figure out how to make custom snippets.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="797-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2797-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="72.214.63.142" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>bsmith@swig505.com</author>
      <description>Great work with this. I've had to use XCode recently and was missing the feel of TextMate. I've added a few more of my favorite TextMate key bindings -- do you have a place I can contribute back for the next guy that gets this?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="797-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>The alias_method_chain of Rake - Override Rake Task </title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/5/26/the-alias_method_chain-of-rake-override-rake-task</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="805bfaa557d4f55491ffe5b99aafcb68" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>The alias_method_chain of Rake - Override Rake Task </description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 02:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2824-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 02:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="77.188.36.94" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>grosser.michael@gmail.com</author>
      <description>something like alias_task_chain would be great :D</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="824-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Interactive JavaScript Console With TextMate</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/7/9/interactive-javascript-console-with-textmate</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="519823a6b60cc8af1e4b97e10cf22c45" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Interactive JavaScript Console With TextMate</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="190.39.195.174" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>and21@hotmail.com</author>
      <description>that font look terrible, even the terminal font look better :D....there are many tricks to smooth it.......</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.90.139.148" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>drgath@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks for sharing.  I'd skip the symlink and just add it to $PATH

export PATH=$PATH:/System/Library/Frameworks/JavaScriptCore.framework/Versions/A/Resources/</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="81.94.17.34" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>klobor@yandex.ru</author>
      <description>@andrew textmate's defult font smoothing (anti-aliasing) is terrible as well - i'd prefer windows' sub-pixel rendering over mac's 3-pixel-thick letters. I wish mac had an option for sub-pixel anti-aliasing too... :(</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LOL, ya'll are commenting on a scaled down graphic converted to a 64-color GIF. The text/font is way better than shown here. Moot too :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="4.59.22.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>aminharis7@gmail.com</author>
      <description>very cool, on a sidenote, what's the code syntax highlighting tool you're using?</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Haris Thanks for the comment. I am using an old version of Mephisto which itself is using CodeRay. More information can &lt;a href="/meta-theme-for-mephisto/css-conventions"&gt;be found here on my blog about my theme and styles for Mephisto&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="24.42.77.98" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>weinstein.josh@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Thanks Ken this is very useful.  This didn't work for me at first, but then I realized that I'd changed my Textmate Ruby (can't remember why; maybe had to do with rvm and jRuby?).  Anyways, replacing: 

#!/usr/bin/env ruby

with:

${TM_RUBY:-/usr/bin/env ruby} &lt;&lt;"[RUBY]" -rcgi

...did the trick.</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="12.167.132.226" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jonathan.m.julian@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Here is a simpler TextMate command to run JavasScript with the jsc. This one does not open a Terminal, it just displays output in a new TextMate pop-up window.

Go to your Bundle Editor, choose New Command

Save: Current File
Input: Selected Text or Document
Output: Show as HTML
Activation: &lt;map to CMD-R&gt;

/System/Library/Frameworks/JavaScriptCore.framework/Versions/A/Resources/jsc "$TM_FILEPATH" | ruby -e 'puts "&lt;pre&gt;#{STDIN.read}&lt;/pre&gt;"'

Click on a different command in the bundle editor to save it. 


One word of warning: jsc is not very good at reporting errors. I usually use spidermonkey because of that reason. Download to ~/spidermonkey, compile, and then use this TextMate command:

~/spidermonkey/js/src/Darwin_DBG.OBJ/js "$TM_FILEPATH" | ruby -e 'puts "&lt;pre&gt;#{STDIN.read}&lt;/pre&gt;"'</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-7" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="12.167.132.226" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jonathan.m.julian@gmail.com</author>
      <description>Yikes. HTML is *not* escaped in comments!

Those commands are:

&lt;p&gt;/System/Library/Frameworks/JavaScriptCore.framework/Versions/A/Resources/jsc "$TM_FILEPATH" | ruby -e 'puts "&amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;#{STDIN.read}&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt;"'

&lt;p&gt;and

&lt;p&gt;~/spidermonkey/js/src/Darwin_DBG.OBJ/js "$TM_FILEPATH" | ruby -e 'puts "&amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;#{STDIN.read}&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt;"'</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-8" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.31.30.176" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>victor.stan@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Or you can install node.js, which uses Google&amp;#8217;s v8 engine and you can use node in the terminal to get an &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IRB&lt;/span&gt; like interface&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-9" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2840-10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="64.120.133.185" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>somatter2012@hotmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;thanks for that ;lol :)),This is great and very helpful.
I look forward to hear from you soon&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="840-10" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>A MacPort/RubyODBC Update</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/7/19/a-macport-rubyodbc-update</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="de596d3500aad63c19b91d2d263b4886" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>A MacPort/RubyODBC Update</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="76.18.246.240" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>tom@themolehill.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So what do you think about &lt;span class="caps"&gt;RVM&lt;/span&gt;?  Is it worth taking on?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love it so far. When it works it&amp;#8217;s wonderful. When it does not. Expect to start supplementing your unix, compiling, etc knowledge real quick!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;RVM&lt;/span&gt; gives you all you need, but it is taking me some time to fix all my edge cases while I setup a CI system for the adapter. I will have another post that covers all that next week or so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="63.227.15.150" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>scott@mobilefoundry.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Interesting. I was wondering why I could never get the utf8 version of the odbc library working with the adapter on Linux. Always thought it must just work on Macs. On Linux when compiling as the utf8 variant the shared library is named odbc_utf8.so, and I could never could find anywhere in the adapter where that shared library could be used. Could only find where odbc.so was used. I don&amp;#8217;t really need utf-8 so I didn&amp;#8217;t dig into it after that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="60.242.128.190" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>adam.meehan@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi Ken&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Just wondered whether you were aware that Ruby &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ODBC&lt;/span&gt; is now a gem?&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;gem install ruby-odbc.&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Which means you can include it as a gem dependency in the main &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SQL&lt;/span&gt; Server gem.&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Unless there is a problem with it?&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Adam&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Adam, I did not know that it was a gem now, tho that is excellent news. Still, we can not include it as a gem dep since that low level transport is technically not required. We still officially support IronRuby which uses the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ADONET&lt;/span&gt; connection mode.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="60.242.128.190" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>adam.meehan@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Forgot about Windows and I actually support apps running on windows with the gem :/&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;But it certainly takes some of the fuss on *nix setup.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2852-6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2010 01:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="173.45.70.99" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jiemeir32@aol.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I could never could find anywhere in the adapter where that shared library could be used. Could only find where odbc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="852-6" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>The RVM Ruby API - Setting Up A CI System For The SQL Server Adapter</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/7/30/the-rvm-ruby-api</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="8548776e6f774d986613ce8e4e3aa494" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>The RVM Ruby API - Setting Up A CI System For The SQL Server Adapter</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 19:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2858-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="80.144.137.99" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>Kd.gundermann@zwick-Edelstahl.de</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thanks Ken!
Very interesting, I will try to do the Same on my Suse testsystem&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="858-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>Protip: Exclude Your RVM Install From Time Machine Backups</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/8/6/protip-exclude-your-rvm-install-from-timemachine-backups</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="3b17768b1f845b48cfc9b6db661ed3f7" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>Protip: Exclude Your RVM Install From Time Machine Backups</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 15:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2863-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2010 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="98.126.0.26" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>melchersg@hotmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is great and very helpful,I will be forwarding it onto my boss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="863-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>How To Clean A Campfire Room Of Uploads</title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/8/19/how-to-clean-a-campfire-room-of-uploads</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="8e697d8525274d59765cde8b477174eb" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>How To Clean A Campfire Room Of Uploads</description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 15:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2867-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="209.213.118.118" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jiemire321@aol.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great tutorial, they are very easy to understand. thanks for that ;-)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="867-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2867-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="98.126.12.106" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jamiee2456@aol.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Oh,can we do like this? I havent heard before the post,thanks for the way of Clean A Campfire Room Of Uploads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="867-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2867-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="195.2.240.68" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>AffinnyThonna@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great information! I&#226;&#8364;&#8482;ve been looking for something like this for a while now. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="867-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <title>TinyTds - A modern, simple and fast FreeTDS library for Ruby using DB-Library </title>
    <link>http://metaskills.net/2010/10/18/tinytds-a-modern-simple-and-fast-freetds-library-for-ruby-using-db-library</link>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://js-kit.com/rss/metaskills.net/"></atom:link>
    <jskit:attribute value="d7eb830cca44d48e7b53eebd35489505" key="md5path"></jskit:attribute>
    <jskit:attribute value="" key="path"></jskit:attribute>
    <description>TinyTds - A modern, simple and fast FreeTDS library for Ruby using DB-Library </description>
    <generator>JS-Kit.com Bulk Site Exporter 0.8</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="202.146.7.239" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>twistedpear@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Neat!&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;#8217;m understanding this correctly then you do not need an &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ODBC&lt;/span&gt; connedtion to use TintTDS, correct?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-0" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;That is correct! Which means no unixODBC or iODBC. It&amp;#8217;s awesome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-1" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="98.126.116.146" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>jamiee8932@aol.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;no unixODBC or iODBC? It is so great!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-2" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="81.0.157.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>knut.stenmark@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Great work, Ken!&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Tried it out for &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MS SQL 2005&lt;/span&gt; and had some difficulties getting it to work at first. Noticed that I had to configure tds version to 4.2 (which did not have anything to do with TinyTds).&lt;/p&gt;


	&lt;p&gt;Will continue to test it.&lt;/p&gt;


One thing on my wish-list: 
	&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support setting of host and port for data server directly in database.yml.
Then it will not be necessary to change freetds.conf&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-3" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="70.169.150.166" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>ken@metaskills.net</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Stonfield Agreed on the zero freetds.conf issue need. I tried looking into that and could not find a way. If you do, file a ticket on the TinyTds github issues page. Re the &amp;#8220;tds version&amp;#8221; thing, no matter what you compile as the default for FreeTDS, the conf setting takes precedence. My testing showed that it was necessary to sync the correct 8.0 version in the client and the conf. I have no idea why and again would love to know a way to bypass the conf (much like a &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DSN&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;less odbc connection) and make that happen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-4" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>jsid-2909-5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <jskit:attribute value="81.0.157.2" key="IP"></jskit:attribute>
      <author>knut.stenmark@gmail.com</author>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;@Ken. I filed a hint on github. It might help you on the way. Let me know if it doesn&amp;#8217;t help. Then I will continue digging.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <jskit:attribute value="909-5" key="sync_peer_3"></jskit:attribute>
      <jskit:attribute value="3" key="foreign"></jskit:attribute>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
